<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<fpdoc-descriptions><package name="fpOdf"><module name="odf_types"><element name="TOdfElement"><short>OdfElement: Basedefinition of all Open-Document-Elements</short>
      </element><element name="TFontFaceDecls"><short>FontFaceDecls definition of the shortcut-node for font-declarations.</short>
      </element><element name="TOdfDocument"><short>OdfDocument basedefintion (it contains! the XMLStructure of the OpenDocument</short>
      </element><element name="TOdfContent"><short>All parts that contain text are based on TOdfContent</short>
      </element><element name="THyperLink"><short>THyperlink is a link to either a point in the document, a file or an url.</short>
      </element><element name="TOdfParagraph"><short>OdfParagraph is the class for a paragraph in the text.</short>
      </element><element name="TSpan"><short>Span is a (small) part of the text with a constant style.</short>
      </element><element name="TBookMark"><short>BookMark is a point in the text the reader can jump to. (see also Hyperlink)</short>
      </element><element name="TOdfTextDocument"><short>OdfTextDocument is the class to use to open, close &amp; modify OpenDocument-Files</short>
      </element><short>fpOdf is a library used to help users to create and to modify OpenDocument Files (ODF)</short>
    <element name="TOdfElement.Find"><short>Find is a general method to find named items when the name of the item is in the attributes</short>
      </element><element name="TOdfTextDocument.Clear"><short>Erase all content and create a new document</short>
      </element><element name="TOdfTextDocument.AddHeadline"><short>Add a heading of a given level </short>
      </element><element name="TOdfContent.AppendText"><short>Appends a text to a content-block</short>
      </element><element name="TOdfTextDocument.AddParagraph"><short>Append a new paragraph of a given style</short>
      </element><element name="TOdfContent.AddSpan" link="TSpan"><short>Add a span to the paragraph</short><descr>A Span is a continuous part of the text with equal style.
</descr><seealso>TSpan
</seealso>
      </element><element name="TOdfContent.AddLineBreak"><short>Appends a (manual) Line-break to the text.</short><descr>a <b>Line-break</b> stops the text at the current position in the line and continues the text at the start of the next line, but all in the same paragraph.
</descr>
      </element><element name="TOdfParagraph.AddBookmark"><short>Adds a bookmark to the paragraph</short>
      </element><element name="TOdfContent.AddLink"><short>appends a link (Hyperlink) to a bookmark</short>
      </element><element name="TOdfContent.AddTab"><short>Appends a tabulator</short>
      </element>
    </module>
  </package>
</fpdoc-descriptions>
